<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AnyBizAI</title><link>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/</link><description>Recent content on AnyBizAI</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Eric Zou</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:28:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Huge Announcement for Browser Support!</title><link>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/browser_support/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 19:00:44 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/post/browser_support/</guid><description>After our inital release on Google Chrome, we realized the demand for our product was greater than ever. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce that we are now supporting all major browsers, including Firefox, Safari, OperaGX, and Microsoft Edge! Now you can biz anywhere, anytime.
Please let us know about any issues here.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/about/</guid><description>About Us Made with ❤️ by the Hugo Bootstrap Theme team.</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/contact/</guid><description>Contact Open an issue on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy TLDR: This website does not use cookies and does not collect any personal data.
Note: The AnyBizAI extension does need to collect personal data and use cookies to help give you the smoothest experience possible. However, this data is not shared by default with any third party. Read more about this policy on our Chrome Web Store page.
Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser.</description></item><item><title>Your AI-Powered Business Partner</title><link>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/page/introducing-anybizai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ezou626.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-autodeployed/page/introducing-anybizai/</guid><description>Introducing AnyBizAI! It&amp;rsquo;s finally here! We&amp;rsquo;re excited to unveil AnyBizAI, a tool to grow any business at any stage. To get started, get our Chrome Extension!
Your Ideas, Our Strategies Simply select any section of your screen that you want to inspect further. AnyBizAI will use state-of-the-art image processing models to aggregate information on businesses related to that section of your screen. See a cool new headline or image? Let us help you figure out how to build a business around it!</description></item></channel></rss>